fundoofun.com 2011-12-01

# Privacy Policy | Fundoofun.com

Fundoofun.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to our Web site visitors’ privacy. Fundoofun.com regards all information collected from its online members as completely confidential. This includes email address provided during the registration processes. Fundoofun.com will never let out your email address to any external parties or any other web sites. Fundoofun.com is firmly committed to the privacy of our users' personal information. Our staff, contractors and others who help us operate our Web site follow this policy on privacy and fair information practices for online activities of Fundoofun.com. We outline here the information collection procedure and usage practices for our Web site. By using this Web site, you agree to accept this Privacy Policy and are aware that our Policy may change over time as discussed below.  

**Cookies**

Our Site uses cookies for delivering content but we do not track any personal user information via these cookies or share this info with any third parties.  

**Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Web site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Web site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the _[Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)_.

**Personal Information**

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties. If in the future we do collect personal information it will be kept completely confidential.

**External Links**

This Site contains links to other sites. Fundoofun.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
